Unit 9 - Even' Star Organic Farm Revisited

## Problem 1.1
1820

## Problem 1.2
Restaurants, CSA

## Problem 1.3
54402.29 - 49956.39 = 4445.9

## Problem 1.4
897

## Problem 2.1
He could increase his prices.
He could reduce the entry cost.
Increasing his prices and/or reducing the entry cost for the farmers' market channel will increase his profits. Reducing the variables costs will not help since they are currently zero, and buying a bigger truck will not help since he currently does not even want to use the truck he has.

## Problem 2.2
Increasing his prices at the farmers' market by 25%

## Problem 2.3
54726.68 

## Problem 2.4
Tomatoes (large), Sweet Potatoes, Winter Squash

## Problem 2.5
CSA, Farmers' Market

## Problem 2.6
No